Anser Shafiq

ansershafiq@gmail.com | (+92) 324 8505960



With a solid foundation in various languages and technologies, including React JS, HTML, CSS, MERN, Python, WordPress, Shopify, Android Studio and React Native, I possess comprehensive knowledge in website and application development. I am passionate about creating web and mobile applications, with a strong emphasis on delivering exceptional user experiences.

WORK HISTORY

WEBSITE DEVELOPER - North American Staffing Services

January 2024 - Working

- Developing, Designing and Managing new websites by using different tool for each.
- Designed well responsive and well maintained website
- Properly can maintain and update the database

Technologies Working On:

- React JS
- WordPress
- JavaScript
- Shopify
- GitHub / Git
- Shoping
- HTML
- CSS

WORDPRESS WEBSITE DEVELOPER - DEVELOPERS ALLEY CO

August 2022 - December 2022

- Designed Many projects assigned to me by company
- Very Good in WooCommerce related projects
- Smooth and fast hand set in designing the views according to need of customer.

Technologies Worked On:

- WordPress
- Woo Commerce
- Elementor
- Divi
- Different Kind Of Themes i.e., Soledad, Astra....

FELLOW WEB DEVELOPER - DEVNATION

May 2021 - January 2022

- Collaborated with senior fellows to build projects using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React
- Built websites by using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Built Web Applications with JavaScirpt, React JS and Firebase.
- Used Github for collaboration and version control.

Technologies Worked On:

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap And JavaScript
- REACT JS And Firebase
- MongoDB
- GitHub/Git
- Python (Data Structure And Algorithms)

EDUCATION

Bachelors Of Science - Computer Science:

University Of Central Punjab, Lahore, Pakistan

2018 - 2023 GPA: 3.12 / 4

FSC Pre Engineering:

Punjab Group Of Colleges, Lahore, Pakistan

2016 - 2018

MATRICULATION:

KIPS School, Lahore, Pakistan

2014 - 2016

SKILLS

- React JS
- MongoDB
- Node JS
- Python
- Express JS
- WordPressShopify
- JavaScript

HTML and CSS

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

TM Staffing Solutions [GitHub/TM-Staffing-Solutions]

- A business website for job recruitment company for display their services facilities to their target clients
- Frontend designed by using React Js and Libraries.
- Libraries used such as React-router-DOM,

Technologies Used: React JS, CSS, E-Mail JS

Let's Construct [GitHub/Lets-Construct]

- Designed an online platform for Customers, Workers(labors, plumbers, constructors, etc..,) and Dealers(cement, concrete, etc..,).
- For customers there are four features, to order worker, to get cost estimation, to get building models and to order products related to construction/building work.
- Worker/Dealers can response to new orders and can see list of orders in process.
- Designed whole project by MERN Stack Development.

Technologies Used: React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB Atlas

LinkedIn - Cloned [GitHub/LinkedIn-Clone]

- Redesigned the LinkedIn website for getting a grip on the use of React and Firebase
- Front end designed by using React and for users data handling used Firebase

Technologies Used: React JS, Firebase, CSS

Work Todo List App [GitHub/TodoList-With-ReactNative]

- A work todo reminder list app
- Listing and the app management scheming to make it useable in all platforms
- Designed Front End By Using React Native along with styles in it.

Technologies Used: React Native, CSS